Stein, Emanuel Additional Arbitration Files: Board of Education Hicksville Public Schools and Hicksville Congress of Teachers 6063
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Emanuel Stein Additional Arbitration Files: Board of Education Hicksville Public Schools and Hicksville Congress of Teachers
1970-1983
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Stein, Emanuel
6063
1.5 cubic feet
1.5 linear ft.
Records.
5791200
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives 227 Ives Hall Tower Road Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheelref@cornell.edu https://catherwood.library.cornell.edu/kheel/
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 09, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, August 18, 2015
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5888: Emanuel Stein Papers
Arbitration, Industrial; Teachers' unions -- New York (State) -- Hicksville; Stein, Emanuel, 1908-1985; Hicksville Public Schools (Hicksville, N.Y.)
5791200
- Form 99, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Hicksville (Box 1, Folder 2)
- UPS - IBT 804 -1154- 82 (Giordana) (Box 1, Folder 3)
- UPS - IBT 1330-1150-82 Lynch 11-12-82, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Rodriguez M-295-81, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Am, AIR- Stokes M-231-81, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- GE IVE 731 3030-8123-82 ND 71244, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- General Electric -IUE Local 182 31 30 0101 82 ND #73030, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- UPS - IBT 804 Colclough 1330-0855-82, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- M-542-81 J.Lane DCA, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Lukas M-457-81, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Am Air M-143-81 Stokes, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Am Air. General, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- American Airlines OKLER 5-6-82, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- American Airlines Arbitration, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- M-01-82 N. Patel M-577-81 J. Sandoval Aair, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Am Air 3-31-82 Bos Noddin, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- American Airlines, Inc. Arbitration, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Pyros, Harey M-444-81, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Speidell - Am. Air M-12-82, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- AA. Sudler, N. M-555-81 3/24/82, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Correspondence - Arbitration: General, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- ATFT Communications CWN Local 1150 ATTC - 84-20 (596), 1983 (Box 2, Folder 18)